Guide to the Sarenco Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, circa 1960s-2000s; Series III
  - 1480-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1481-X, Sarenco, Ousmane Ndiaye Dago (Box 6)
  - 1482-Jean-François Bory, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1483-Lamberto Pignotti (Box 6)
  - 1484-Un'opera di Pignotti (Box 6)
  - 1485-Un'opera di Pignotti (Box 6)
  - 1486-Un'opera di Pignotti (Box 6)
  - 1487-Pierre Garnier (Box 6)
  - 1488-Lamberto Pignotti (Box 6)
  - 1489-Krel Trinkewitz con una sua opera (Box 6)
  - 1490-Frau Novak, Ladislav Novak (Box 6)
  - 1491-Ladislav Novak (Box 6)
  - 1492-Richard Martel in performance (Box 6)
  - 1493-Richard Martel in performance (Box 6)
  - 1494-Richard Martel in poerformance (Box 6)
  - 1495-Ladislav Novak (Box 6)
  - 1496-Richard Martel in performance (Box 6)
  - 1497-Richard Martel in performance (Box 6)
  - 1498-Jean-François Bory in performance (Box 6)
  - 1499-Richard Martel in performance (Box 6)
  - 1500-Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1501-Jean-François Bory in performance (Box 6)
  - 1502-Un'opera di Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1503-Jean-François Bory in performance (Box 6)
  - 1504-Un'opera di Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1505-Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1506-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1507-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1508-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1509-Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1510-Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1511-Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1512-Jean-François Bory mentre realizza un'opera (Box 6)
  - 1513-Jean-François Bory mentre realizza un'opera (Box 6)
  - 1514-Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1515-Jean-François Bory in un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1516-Jean-François Bory in un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1517-Jean-François Bory in performance (Box 6)
  - 1518-Jiri Kolar e Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1519-Jean-François Bory in un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1520-Jean-François Bory in un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1521-Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1522-Un'opera di Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1523-Jean-François Bory, Alain Arias-Misson (Box 6)
  - 1524-Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1525-Jean-François Bory in performance (Box 6)
  - 1526-Jean-François Bory in performance (Box 6)
  - 1527-Jean-François Bory in performance (Box 6)
  - 1528-Jean-François Bory in un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1529-Due opere di Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1530-Un'opera di jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1531-Sarenco, Giuseppe Chiari (Box 6)
  - 1532-Un'opera di Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1533-Jean-François Bory in performance (Box 6)
  - 1534-Sarenco e Bory with friends (Box 6)
  - 1535-Sarenco, Giuseppe Chiari (Box 6)
  - 1536-Jean-François Bory, Sarenco, X,X,X,Ugo Carrega, Julien Blaine, Franco Verdi (Box 6)
  - 1537-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1538-Jean-François Bory in performance (Box 6)
  - 1539-Jean-Jacques Lebel, Tibor Papp, Julien Blaine, Jean-François Bory, Bernard Heidsieck (Box 6)
  - 1540-Un'opera di Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1541-Jean Dupuy (Box 6)
  - 1542-Bruno Munari (Box 6)
  - 1543-X,X,X, Beppe Morra, Sarenco, Bruno Munari (Box 6)
  - 1544-Jean-François Bory in performance (Box 6)
  - 1545-Jean Dupuy (Box 6)
  - 1546-Un'opera di Jean Dupuy (Box 6)
  - 1547-Jean Dupuy (Box 6)
  - 1548-Jean Dupuy (Box 6)
  - 1549-Una mostra di Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1550-Jean-François Bory, Alain Arias-Misson (Box 6)
  - 1551-Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1552-Un'opera di Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1553-Jean Dupuy (Box 6)
  - 1554-Fernando Millan (Box 6)
  - 1555-Jean-François Bory in performance (Box 6)
  - 1556-Sarenco, Ladislav Novak (Box 6)
  - 1557-X, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1558-Bruno Munari, Sarenco, X (Box 6)
  - 1559-Bruno Munari, Sarenco, X (Box 6)
  - 1560-Bruno Munari, Sarenco, Beppe Morra, X, X, X (Box 6)
  - 1561-Sarenco, Bruno Munari, Beppe Morra, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1562-Sarenco, Bruno Munari, Beppe Morra, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1563-Sarenco, Bruno Munari, X,X (Box 6)
  - 1564-Sarenco, Bruno Munari, X,X (Box 6)
  - 1565-Sarenco, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1566-Beppe Morra, Bruno Munari, Sarenco, X, X, X (Box 6)
  - 1567-Sarenco, Beppe Morra, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1568-Sarenco, Beppe Morra, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1569-Un'opera di Lamberto Pignotti (Box 6)
  - 1570-Un'opera di Lamberto Pignotti (Box 6)
  - 1571-Una mostra di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1572-Giorgio Cortenova, Guido Almansi, Egidio Mucci, Sarenco, Lamberto Pignotti, X (Box 6)
  - 1573-Giorgio Cortenova, Guido Almansi, Egidio Mucci, Sarenco, Lamberto Pignotti, X (Box 6)
  - 1574-Sarenco, X, Lamberto Pignotti, X (Box 6)
  - 1575-Sarenco, X, Lamberto Pignotti, X (Box 6)
  - 1576-Un'opera di Lamberto Pignotti (Box 6)
  - 1577-Un'opera di Lamberto Pignotti (Box 6)
  - 1578-Un'opera di Lamberto Pignotti (Box 6)
  - 1579-Sarenco, Beppe Morra, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1580-Sarenco, Beppe Morra, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1581-Sarenco, Beppe Morra, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1582-Sarenco, Beppe Morra, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1583-Beppe Morra, Sarenco, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1584-Beppe Morra, sarenco, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1585-Sarenco, Bruno Munari,X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1586-Sarenco, Beppe Morra, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1587-Sarenco, Beppe Morra, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1588-Sarenco, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1589-Beppe Morra, Sarenco, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1590-Sarenco, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1591-Bruno Munari, Sarenco, Beppe Morra, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1592-Bruno Munari, sarenco, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1593-Sarenco, Bruno Munari, Beppe Morra, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1594-Sarenco, bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1595-Beppe Morra, Sarenco, Bruno Munari,X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1596-Bruno Munari, Sarenco, Beppe Morra, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1597-Bruno Munari, Sarenco, Beppe Morra, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1598-Sarenco, Bruno Munari (Box 6)
  - 1599-Un'opera di Pierre Garnier (Box 6)
  - 1600-Jean-François Bory in performance (Box 6)
  - 1601-Jean-François Bory (Box 6)
  - 1602-Jean-François Bory, Sarenco, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1603-Sarenco, Bruno Munari, Beppe Morra, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1604-Bruno Munari (Box 6)
  - 1605-Aldo Mondino, Sarenco, Franca Vignati, Auguste Galli, Ignazio Moncada, Vittorio Gelmetti (Box 6)
  - 1606-Sarenco, X, Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1607-Patrizia Guerresi in performance (Box 6)
  - 1608-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1609-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1610-Bruno Munari (Box 6)
  - 1611-Bruno Munari (Box 6)
  - 1612-Paolo Berardelli, Bruno Munari, Giuseppe Desiato (Box 6)
  - 1613-Bruno Munari, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1614-Beppe Morra, Sarenco, Bruno Munari, X,X,X (Box 6)
  - 1615-Bruno Munari, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1616-Paolo Berardelli, Bruno Munari, Giuseppe Desiato (Box 6)
  - 1617-Sarenco's father, Sarenco, Sarenco's mother (Box 6)
  - 1618-Sarenco's father in performance (Box 6)
  - 1619-Sarenco's father in performance (Box 6)
  - 1620-Sarenco in performance (Box 6)
  - 1621-Sarenco in performance con la figlia Eva (Box 6)
  - 1622-Sarenco in performance (Box 6)
  - 1623-Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1624-Sarenco in performance con la figlia Eva (Box 6)
  - 1625-Sarenco in performance con la figlia Eva (Box 6)
  - 1626-Sarenco, Fernando Millan (Box 6)
  - 1627-Sarenco in performance con la figlia Eva (Box 6)
  - 1628-Sarenco, X,X, Innocente, Luigi Meneghelli, Aldo Mondino (Box 6)
  - 1629-Sarenco performance (Box 6)
  - 1630-Sarenco performance (Box 6)
  - 1631-Sarenco performance (Box 6)
  - 1632-Sarenco performance (Box 6)
  - 1633-Sarenco, Patrizia Guerresi (Box 6)
  - 1634-Musician in Sarenco performance (Box 6)
  - 1635-Sarenco in performance (Box 6)
  - 1636-Eva in Sarenco performance (Box 6)
  - 1637-X, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1638-Sarenco performance (Box 6)
  - 1639-X, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1640-Eva in Sarenco performance (Box 6)
  - 1641-Sarenco, Eva, X,X (Box 6)
  - 1642-Sarenco e amici in un'installazione di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1643-Sarenco, Martina Corgnati, X,X (Box 6)
  - 1644-Sarenco, Pierre Garnier (Box 6)
  - 1645-Carlo Belloli (Box 6)
  - 1646-Sarenco performance (Box 6)
  - 1647-Musicista in una performance di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1648-Un film di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1649-Sarenco in performance (Box 6)
  - 1650-Luigi Bonotto, Sarenco, X (Box 6)
  - 1651-X, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1652-Musicista in una performance di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1653-Musicista in una performance di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1654-Fabrizio Garghetti, Sarenco, X (Box 6)
  - 1655-Sarenco in performance con la figlia Eva (Box 6)
  - 1656-Grazia Azzali, Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1657-Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1658-Sarenco performance (Box 6)
  - 1659-Sarenco performance (Box 6)
  - 1660-Sarenco, X (Box 6)
  - 1661-X, Sarenco, Fabrizio Dal Santo (Box 6)
  - 1662-Sarenco a Barcellona (Box 6)
  - 1663-Sarenco a Barcellona (Box 6)
  - 1664-Sarenco a Barcellona (Box 6)
  - 1665-Sarenco in performance (Box 6)
  - 1666-Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1667-Sarenco in performance (Box 6)
  - 1668-Musicista in una performance di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1669-Eva in una performance di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1670-Una performance di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1671-Una performance di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1672-Un'installazione di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1673-Amici in una installazione di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1674-Amici in una installazione di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1675-Roland Sabatier (Box 6)
  - 1676-Roland Sabatier (Box 6)
  - 1677-Sarenco e una sua installazione (Box 6)
  - 1678-Julien Blaine (Box 6)
  - 1679-Fabrizio Garghetti, Sarenco, Gianni Bertini (Box 6)
  - 1680-Sarenco, X, Julien Blaine, Martina Corgnati (Box 6)
  - 1681-Luciano Parise, Adriano Parise, Julien Blaine, Ugo Carrega, X (Box 6)
  - 1682-Maurice Lemaitre (Box 6)
  - 1683-Amici in una installazione di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1684-Nicholas Zurbrugg, Sarenco, Giorgio Cortenova, Enrico Mascelloni (Box 6)
  - 1685-Amici in una installazione di Sarenco (Box 6)
  - 1686-Maurice Lemaitre (Box 6)
  - 1687-X, Fernando Millan (Box 6)
  - 1688-X, Fernando Millan (Box 6)
- Artwork, 1960-2012; Series IV
  Artwork is arranged by artist name.
  - Demosthenes Agrafiotis [293], 1998 (Box 7 (Broadside))
  - Fernando Aguiar [355, 359], 1996 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Almagul [300, 301], undated (Box 9 (Broadside))
  - Julien Blaine [354, 356, 360], 1998 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Julien Blaine [316], 1998 (Box 10 (Broadside))
  - Julien Blaine [286], 1998 (Box 11 (Broadside))
  - Julien Blaine [295, 296], 2000, 2007 (Box 12 (Broadside))
  - Julien Blaine [43, 362-391], undated (Box 13)
  - Monty Cantsin [340-353], undated (Box 14)
  - Ugo Carrega [74], 1970 (Box 15 (Broadside))
  - Ugo Carrega [61], 1992 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Ugo Carrega [62], 1997 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Ugo Carrega [63, 64], 2002 (Box 16 (Broadside))
  - Ugo Carrega [65, 66], 2002 (Box 17 (Broadside))
  - Ugo Carrega [67, 68], 2002 (Box 18 (Broadside))
  - Ugo Carrega [69, 70], 2002 (Box 19 (Broadside))
  - Ugo Carrega [71, 72], 2002 (Box 20 (Broadside))
  - Ugo Carrega [76, 77], 2002 (Box 21 (Broadside))
  - Ugo Carrega [78, 79], 2002 (Box 22 (Broadside))
  - Ugo Carrega [60], 2003 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Ugo Carrega [357, 358], 2004 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Ugo Carrega [unnumbered], 2007 (Box 23 (Broadside))
  - Giuseppe Chiari [305, 306], undated (Box 24 (Broadside))
  - Hans Clavin [1], 1989-1990 (Box 25)
  - Mario Diacono [298], 1967 (Box 26 (Broadside))
  - Luc Fierens [45-53], 2010, 2012 (Box 27)
  - Giovanni Fontana [317], 1998 (Box 28 (Broadside))
  - John Furnival [308, 310, 311], undated (Box 29 (Broadside))
  - John Furnival [309, 339], undated (Box 30 (Broadside))
  - Jiri Kolar [297], 1963 (Box 31 (Broadside))
  - Lucia Marcucci [44], 2006 (Box 27)
  - Fernando Millan [291], 1998 (Box 32 (Broadside))
  - Seiichi Niikuni [287], 1966 (Box 33 (Broadside))
  - Ladislav Novak [294], 1998 (Box 34 (Broadside))
  - Ladislav Novak [394-408], 1960 (Box 35)
  - Ladislav Novak [409-422, 632], undated (Box 36)
  - Clemente Padin [54-59], 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - Michelle Perfetti [393], 1971 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [177], 1963-1993 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [616], 1963 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [176], 1963 (Box 39 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [164], 1963 (Box 40 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [629], 1966 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [627], 1969 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [153, 154, 156], 1969 (Box 41 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [85, 155, 158, 159, 161], 1971 (Box 42 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [281], 1972 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [315, 320], 1972 (Box 43 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [302, 304, 314, 321], 1972 (Box 44 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [303, 312, 313, 423], 1972 (Box 45 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [322, 323, 327-329], 1974 (Box 46 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [326, 330-332], 1974 (Box 47 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [307, 424], 1976, 1995 (Box 48 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [607, 620, 623], 1978 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [325], 1979 (Box 49 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [324], 1979 (Box 50 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [289], 1989 (Box 51 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [189, 208, 210, 217, 221, 226, 236, 237, 240, 247, 252, 254, 258, 260, 266, 270, 275, 279], 1993 (Box 52 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [3-41], 1997-2007 (Box 53)
  - Sarenco [288], 1997 (Box 54 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [361, 432, 440, 458, 462, 475, 476, 488, 505, 509, 510, 525, 546, 561, 572, 590, 592, 597], 1998 (Box 55 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [285], 1998? (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [12-13, 178-188], 1998, undated (Box 56 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [318], 1998 (Box 57 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [319], 1998 (Box 58 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [75], 1999 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [292], 2001 (Box 59 (Broadside))
  - Sarenco [392], 2002 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [280, 299, 333-338], 2004 (Box 55 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [2, 42], 2005, undated (Box 60)
  - Sarenco [425], 2005? (Box 55 (Oversize))
  - Sarenco [282-284], 2010 (Box 8 (Oversize))
- Artist and photocopy books, 1971-2012; Series V
  Artist and photocopy books are arranged in the order in which they were received.
  - 1-Ladislav Novak 'Disegni topologici', 1990 (Box 61)
  - 2-Julien Blaine 'Parodies & Brouillons', undated (Box 61)
  - 3-Sarenco 'Mantua me captavit', 1997 (Box 61)
  - 4-Sarenco 'Il meno è il nome', 2004 (Box 61)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes photographs.
  - 5-Sarenco 'Douleur africaine', 2008 (Box 61)
  - 6-Sarenco '20 nuovi collages e tutte le poesie del 90', 1990 (Box 61)
  - 7-Sarenco '20 nuovi collages e tutte le poesie del 90', 1990 (Box 61)
  - 8-Sarenco 'Enea Ferrari e Piero Manzoni', 1972 (Box 61)
  - 9-Sarenco's, 1996 (Box 61)
  - 10- What is necessary to know about Sarenco', 2004 (Box 61)
  - 11-Sarenco 'Stedelijk Museum', 1972 (Box 61)
  - 12-Blaine, Innocente, Sarenco, 2004 (Box 61)
    Includes original art.
  - 13-Jean-François Bory 'Poésies provisoires', 1990 (Box 61)
  - 14-Monty Cantsin, 1998 (Box 61)
  - 15-Sarenco 'Opporre opposizione', 2003 (Box 61)
  - 16-Tre poeti d'Europa, 2005 (Box 62)
  - 17-Sarenco 'Aberrare poeticum', 1989 (Box 62)
  - 18-Sarenco 'E.A. POEsia', 2003 (Box 62)
  - 19-Sarenco '54 poesie d'amore', 1995 (Box 62)
    Includes collage elements.
  - 20-Nahl Nucha 'Nodiden', 1971 (Box 62)
  - 21-Nahl Nucha 'Nodiden', 1971 (Box 62)
  - 22-Hermann Damen, 1974 (Box 62)
  - 23-Subvers, 1974 (Box 62)
  - 24-Subvers, 1972 (Box 62)
  - 25-Sarenco 'Opporre opposizione', 2003 (Box 62)
  - 26-Sarenco 'Fuochi d'artificio', 2004 (Box 62)
  - 27-Sarenco 'Il meno è il nome', 2004 (Box 62)
  - 28-Absolute Mail-Art, 1998 (Box 62)
  - 29-Sarenco: Il viaggio, 2006 (Box 63)
  - 30-Subvers, 1974 (Box 63)
  - 31-Sarenco 'Poesia', 2011 (Box 63)
  - 32-Sarenco: Play Cards, 2004 (Box 63)
  - 33-Sarenco: Azulejos and Company, 2004 (Box 63)
  - 34-Sarenco 'Installazioni', 2006 (Box 63)
    Artist book
  - 35-Subvers, 1974 (Box 63)
  - 36-Herman De Vries, 1974 (Box 63)
  - 37-Subvers, 1974 (Box 63)
  - 38-Sarenco 'Tutto quello che si deve sapere di Sarenco', 2004 (Box 63)
  - 39-Ugo Carrega 'Dalla mente in poi', 1989 (Box 63)
  - 40-Fernando Millan 'Libro des Hecho a mano', undated (Box 63)
  - 41-Sarenco 'Beretta s,p,a.', 2004 (Box 63)
  - 42-Sarenco 'Ma esiste un'anima ?', 1972 (Box 64)
  - 43-L'oro di Praga, 1999 (Box 64)
  - 44-Sarenco, 1998 (Box 64)
  - 45-Pierre Garnier, 2007 (Box 64)
  - 46-Fernando Millan, 1993 (Box 64)
  - 47-Gérard Fioretti, 2005; 1 (Box 65)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - 48-Sarenco, 1998 (Box 64)
  - 49-Shozo Shimamoto, 1999 (Box 64)
  - 50-Pierre Garnier, 2002 (Box 64)
  - 51-Gian Paolo Roffi, undated (Box 64)
  - 52-Sarenco, 2004 (Box 64)
  - 53-Hans Clavin, 2012 (Box 64)